UNITE Pacific Northwest District Council Files 6000/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Pacific Northwest District Council Files
1992-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Pacific Northwest District Council
6000/018
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Records.
8239536
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 04, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780/207: ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Records 5780/207 AV: ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Audio-Visual Materials 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/018 P: UNITE Pacific Northwest District Council Photographs
Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing trade--New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Pacific Northwest District Council; UNITE HERE (Organization)
8239536
- Macy's (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Press Pack (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Press Kit, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Oct.
- Columbus Dispatch - Sweatshops (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Tuesday November 5 - Election Day (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Precinct Tally Street (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Statewide Informations Systems (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NAFTA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  June 6
- Fast Track, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  November
- Mabel Teng (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NAFTA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  November 5
- Diou Arouer (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Proposition 208 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Election 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- UNITE! (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Fascimile Transmission Cover (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Conf.Mayors - Press Conf. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Post Office Uniforms (Box 1, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 19)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  June
- K Quan Corres., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  May
- K Quan Corres., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  April
- K Quan Corres., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  March
- K Quan Corres., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  February
- K Quan Corres., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  January
- K. Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  December
- K Quan Corres., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  October
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  September
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  August
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  July
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- K Quan correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- K quan Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- K Quan Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Misc. Corres. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Misc. Corresp., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Misc. Corresp. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Misc. Corresp. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Misc. Corresp. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Misc. Corresp. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Misc. Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Misc.Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Misc. Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- K Quan Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- K Quan Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- K Quan Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- K Quan Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- K Quan Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- K Quan Corresp., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Automobile Log (Box 2, Folder 24)
- D. Tutson Auto Log, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- UNITE! Memo (Box 3, Folder 1)
- NLC (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Board of Trustees Next Meeting, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  December 9
- Board of Trustees (BoT) Next Meeting, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  October 25
- BoT Next Meeting, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  August 22
- BoT Next Meeting, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  April 25
- Alde Shop Issues, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Alde Shop Issues, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Advance Pleating Shop Issues, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bay Bias Shop Issues, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Garment 2000, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Fashion West, Inc. Meeting, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- CIR: Coalition Immigrant Rights Board (Box 3, Folder 13)
- CIR - 10th Anniversary Campaign (Box 3, Folder 14)
- CIRRS: Coalition for Immigrant & Refugee Rights & Services (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Henning Center, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Labor Project for Working Families (Box 3, Folder 17)
- SFSU Labor Advisory Board (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Supt. Committee Mequiladoras Workers (Box 3, Folder 19)
- 98 Sweatshop Workers (Box 3, Folder 20)
- 97 Sweatshop Watch (Box 3, Folder 21)
- 96 Sweatshop Watch (Box 3, Folder 22)
- 96 Sweatshop Stationary (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 95 Sweatshop Doc. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- US Conference on Mayors, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Sweatshop Watch, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Center for Labor Research and Education (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Center for Labor Research UC Berkeley, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  May 28
- US/Guatemala Education Project (Box 3, Folder 29)
- UCB Labor Center Advisory Board (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Center for Labor Research and Education (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Labor in the Global Economy Working Committee (Box 3, Folder 32)
- UCB Labor Center Global Conference, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- UNITE! Materials (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Tim Hayes Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bebe, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Lafa (Box 4, Folder 4)
- K-Mart, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Recreation Wear, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Win Fashion (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Resume Staff (Box 4, Folder 8)
- GIDC/Misc. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Articles/Back Wages (Box 4, Folder 10)
- IRS Forms Political (Box 4, Folder 11)
- AB633 Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Immigration Update 2001 Update (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Work Party (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Ergonomics (Box 4, Folder 15)
- UNITE! Fascimile Transmittal (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Re: Legislative Department (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Political UNITE! (Box 4, Folder 18)
- CAL Industrial Relation Dept. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Senator Barbara Boxer (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Gray Davis (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Carole Migdene (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Barbara Lee (Box 4, Folder 23)
- George Miller (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Nancy Pelosi (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Mike Thompson (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Governor Davis (Box 4, Folder 27)
- AB 3046 Media (Box 4, Folder 28)